way back in 2007 my ex gave me this book
book by Francisco colico titled Mo back
then it led me to a lot of realizations
in life foreign
this time it showed me that you need to
save for emergencies you need to protect
basically to protect your income
by means of life insurance you need to
invest your money for it to grow for
long term and even the idea later in
life you might want to transfer your
accumulated wealth to your families that
was the time when I started investing on
my own except before
insurance
I realized
if there is someone who would be
depending on your income you need to
protect your income and one way to
protect your income is to get the life
insurance why because getting a life
insurance can expand your income for a
certain period of time with a little
cash amount needed I got invited to this
insurance company that I got my
insurance policies in the seminar I
never really thought of myself working
in a sales kind of industry bucket one
I'm a very introvert
personally talking to a lot of people
talking to strangers but then again what
made me stay in Sun Life
very fulfilling career in Sun Life We
Make a Difference by helping other
people secure their finances and achieve
their goals and dreams in life second I
saw the importance of time
life since
you have a lot of time for your family
you're not at the mercy of your boss
looking back I enjoy company my kids to
their field trips second I like the
recognitions bucket the recognition life
uh you are recognized for your hard work
if you hit a certain level
medallions or trophies
stage katima Awards night another thing
here in Sun Life and very dedicated to
work more if you qualify you can travel
local and abroad for free at all expense
paid
well I'm inviting you take a look at
this career if you want to be part of
this kind of environment of this kind of
culture wherein there is no limitation
on growth and potential then I'd like
you to join our team if you are
ambitious and obedient just do it and
we'll see the top